videolean.com 2019-04-09

# Videolean - Make your own video online - Professional, Fast and Affordable

Personal information collected by Videolean will be used for the proper service delivery and Web management. This includes traffic management within the site aiming to internal management purposes or advertising. 

The data collected will be transferred to companies belonging to the group, aimed to their own marketing purposes or notification of services. As well as to companies collaborating with the management of Web or the services offered in it. This includes the banks or companies which manage the charges / payments related to the service offered as well as to companies managing third-party advertising. 

Such assigned data will be the strictly essentials regarding the services rendered by each of such companies or persons. 

Meideistudio, S.L.U. owns the website, www.videolean.com , and exposes in this section the Corporate Privacy Policy concerning the personal information that users can provide while visiting any website of Wolters Kluwer Spain 

The Privacy Policy of Meideistudio, SLU (hereinafter Videolean), is based on the compliance with current legislation regarding the protection of personal data: Law 15/1999 of 13 December on the Ley de Protección de datos (LOPD) and Real Decreto 1720/2007 of 21 December, which approves the Reglamento de Desarrollo de la Ley Orgánica 15/1999 (RLOPD). 

  1. **Information**

The information received by Meideistudio, S.L.U. through its Web sites will be treated with the highest confidentiality. Videolean will observe constantly the existing rules on data protection, in particular, the Ley Orgánica de Protección de Datos de Carácter Personal15/1999 of December 13, and will take the necessary steps to, in relation to such data, prevent alteration, loss, and unauthorized access, as well as the duty of secrecy on the subject of data protection and other applicable confidentiality obligations. Likewise, Meideistudio agrees not to use the personal data of registered users on the Websites for other purposes outside the object of the procurement of the services provided. 

According to current legislation, Videolean collects personal data related with the users and professionals registered on the Websites and includes them in a file which Videolean owns and for which treatment is exclusively aimed for the purpose of managing the services requested to the Company and answer queries that users and professionals can make. The entity responsible for the files is Meideistudio, S.L.U. 

The User must provide the data and personal circumstances required in the registration form in order to register as a customer service and / or to make payment corresponding to the contract to provide services (name or company name, email address, address, country of residence). The registration of this information is required; the lack of complementation of this information by the user or providing incorrect information will allow to Videolean to deny the service at any time. The user or professional can omit or fail to communicate any data or personal circumstance that is not absolutely necessary for a customer log in or contract formalization. 

  2. **Use of information**

Likewise, the Web Site User expressly agrees that the data and content entered by himself, while doing the registration or doing the normal Videolean usage - described in the Terms and Conditions, concerning his own business , are included in a automated file owned by Meideistudio, SLU 

Adicionalmente, el Usuario consiente el tratamiento de sus datos con la finalidad de informarle, por cualquier medio, incluido el correo electrónico, de los cambios o novedades en la política, actividad o de productos y servicios de Meideistudio, S.L.U. o de terceras empresas colaboradoras. 

Videolean will be able to use third companies to make measurements or monitoring aimed at efficient management of the Website and services or advertising websites in order to put ads on the website Videolean. These companies may use cookies or other instruments to measure the effectiveness of their advertising. 

At the same time, the client accepts that the email address provided at the time of registration is the contact address to inform about any act within the purview of Meideistudio, SLU., which may be required by Law 15/1999 to communicate to the Customer. 

Likewise, the client expressly consents Videolean to communicate the necessary data to companies or banks needed to manage and / or charge the service. 

  3. **Data: Right of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition**

In case of failure to authorize processing of your data for the purpose stated in the previous section, the user may exercise his right to object to treatment, through an email with the reference "Data Protection" to the E-mail address info @ motion4startups . com or by signed written request sent by certified mail to the following address: 

> Meideistudio, S.L.U. ; Carretera. General. de Tamaraceite, 92 1º A 35018 de Las Palmas de Gran Canaria (España). 

This same mechanism mentioned in the previous paragraph, shall be established for the exercise of the rights that are legally established such as access, editing and deleting Data collected by Videolean may be processed and stored in Spain or any other country containing data storage facilities. Likewise, Videolean may conduct international transfers of data to countries outside the EU under the express consent of the client, all in accordance with the provisions of the law. 

Specifically, Videolean provides to registered users and professionals a mechanism within the Web sites to delete the files automatically. 

That is, Videolean will provide users and professionals registered a mechanism to erase their information automatically from the files. 

  4. **Security in treatment: computer processing and data custody**

Videolean declares and warrants that holds security levels for the protection of personal data as provided by legislation, and has established all the technical means at its disposal to prevent the loss, misuse, alteration, unauthorized access and theft of data provided by users. All this does not alter the fact that the user or professional expressly accepts that Internet security is not impregnable. 

  5. **Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of information needed to identify the user during the online visit of our website and for the lapse of time it is connected. The browser of the client stores cookies on his hard drive during the current session only occupying a minimal memory space and not harming the computer. The cookies do not contain any specific personal information, and most of them are deleted from hard drive to end the browser session (so-called session cookies). 

Most browsers accept cookies as standard and, regardless of the cookies, they allow or prevent within security settings, the temporary or memorized cookies. 

Without users' express consent, by enabling cookies in their browser-Videolean will not link within cookies, the stored data with user´s personal data provided at the time of registration or purchase. 

  6. **Modification of Privacy Policy**

Videolean reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy here exposed, according to its own judgment or by reason of a change in legislation, jurisprudence or doctrine of the Spanish Agency for Data Protection. 

Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be posted to the Web before its effective implementation. The mere use of the site or access through passwords after such changes will constitute acceptance of these.
